Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Nationalsocialistiche Deutsche Arbeiter Partei -- Views., 59 items (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Nature Study -- Views. Folder 1 of 2., 87 items (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Nature Study -- Views. Folder 2 of 2., 78 items (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Neal Family., 1 item (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Nebraska -- Views., 6 items (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Nederland, Colo. -- Views., 1 item (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Needles, Calif. -- Views., 64 items (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Negroes -- Portraits., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Negroes -- San Diego -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Nelson, Horatio Nelson, viscount, 1758-1805, -- Portrait. (Folder 9)
- Neutra, Richard Joseph, 1892-1970, -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Nevada -- Views., 3 items (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Nevada City, Calif., 11 items (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Neve, Felipe de -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 51, Folder 11)
- New Jersey -- Views., 1 item (Box 51, Folder 12)
- New Mexico -- Views. (Box 96, Folder 7)
- New Mexico -- Views., 33 items (Box 51, Folder 13)
- New Mexico. College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts, State College -- Views., 33 items (Box 51, Folder 14)
- New Mexico. University -- Views., 20 items (Folder 15)
- New Port Beach -- Views. (Box 99, Folder 5)
- New York (State) -- Views. Folder 1 of 2., 44 items (Box 52, Folder 1)
- New York (State) -- Views. Folder 2 of 2., 16 items (Folder 2)
- New York City., 84 items (Folder 16)
- New Zealand -- Views., 21 items (Folder 3)
- Newberry, John Strong, 1822-1892., 1 item (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Newberry, Perry -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Newhall Pass, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 4 items (Folder 6)
- Newman, Francis William, 1805-1897., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Newman, John Henry, Cardinal, 1801-1890., 2 items (Folder 8)
- Newman, John Philip, 1826-1899., 1 item (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Newmark, Marco., 1 item (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Newton, Alfred Edward., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Newton, I.B., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Niagra Falls., 8 items (Folder 13)
- Nice -- Views, 10 items (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Nightingale, Florence, 1820-1910., 3 items (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Nin, Anais, 1903-1977., 12 items (Folder 16)
- Noble, Cyrus., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Noble, Raymond Goodman, 1873-1945., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Noble, Robert B. -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 52, Folder 18)
- No?, Am?d?e de, 1819-1879, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Nordhoff, Charles, 1830-1901., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Nordholt Family -- Portrait., 5 items (Folder 22)
- Norris, George William, 1861-1944., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Norris, Kathlene (Thompson), 1880-1966, -- Portrait. (Box 96, Folder 8)
- North Dakota -- Views., 27 items (Box 53, Folder 1)
- North, John Welsley, 1815-1890 -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Norway -- Views., 32 items (Folder 2)
- Novello, Clara Anastasia, countess Gigliucci, 1818-1908., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Noyo, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Nuremberg., 12 items (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Oakland, Calif., 5 items (Folder 6)
- Ocean Park., 4 items (Folder 7)
- Ochoa, Estevan., 2 items (Folder 8)
- Oden, George J., 1 item (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Offices -- Views., 1 item (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Ogden, Utah -- Views., 3 items (Folder 11)
- Oil Fields -- Calif., 7 items (Folder 12)
- Ojai Valley, Calif. -- Views., 11 items (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Okinawa Island -- Views., 31 items (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Oklahoma City., 1 item (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Olds, Ransom Eli, 1864-1950., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Oliphant, Margaret Oliphant (Wilson), 1828-1897, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Olson, Culbert Levy, 1876-1962, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Olvera, Agustin., 2 items (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Olympic Games, Los Angeles, 1932 -- Views., 15 items (Box 53, Folder 20)
- O'Melveny, Henry Williams, 1859-1941, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 21)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone, 1888-1953, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Ontario., 5 items (Folder 23)
- Oregon -- Views (Coast Highways)., 13 items (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Oregon -- Views., 9 items (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Oregon City, Ore. -- Views., 1 item (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Ori A Ori., 2 items (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Oro Grande, N.M. -- Views., 9 items (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Orsini Family -- Views., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Ortega Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Folder 6)
- Osbourne, H.Z., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Oscar II, King of Sweden, 1829-1907, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 8)
- O'Shaugnnessy, Arthur William Edgar, 1844-1881, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Ossa, de la, Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Otis, Harrison Gray, 1837-1917, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Ouray, Colo. -- Views., 27 items (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Oury, William S., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Overill Rancho, Colusa Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Owens River -- Views., 2 items (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Owens Valley, Calif. -- Views., 9 items (Folder 17)
- Owens, E.H., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Oxnard, Calif. -- Views., 32 items (Folder 18)
- Pacific Electric Railway Company -- Views. (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Pacific Grove, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Pacific Palisades, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Folder 20)
- Pacific Southwest Exposition, Long Beach, 1928., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Packman, Ana Begue., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Paddle Steamers -- Views., 15 items (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Paddock, H.T., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Paderewski, Ignace, 1860-1941 -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 26)
- Pagosa Springs, Colo. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 27)
- Painted Canyon., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Pala, San Diego Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Palisade, Nev. -- Views., 3 items (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Pallette, Caroline Elizabeth (Cartwright), -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Palm Springs., 18 items (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Palmerston, Henry John Temple, 3rd viscount, 1784-1865., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Palo Alto, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 34)
- Palomar, Mount., 5 items (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Palomares Family., 2 items (Box 54, Folder 36)
- Palos Verdes Estates, Calif., 30 items (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Panguitch Lake, Utah -- Views., 2 items (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Pankhurst, Emmeline (Goulden), 1858-1928., 1 item (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Panorama of Caracas and Scene in Gardens, Trinidad. (Folder 1)
- Papuans -- Portraits., 6 items (Folder 39)
- Paraiso Springs, N.M. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 1)
- Paris -- Views., 21 items (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Paris, Comte de., 1 item (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Parish, John Carl., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Park City, Utah -- Views., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Parker, C.C., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Parr, Harriett, 1828-1900, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Parrott, John -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Pasadena -- Views (Agriculture)., 3 items (Folder 11)
- Pasadena -- Views (Buildings)., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Pasadena -- Views (Busch's Garden)., 26 items (Folder 13)
- Pasadena -- Views (Business Enterprises)., 9 items (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Pasadena -- Views (Churches)., 15 items (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Pasadena -- Views (Clubs)., 3 items (Folder 16)
- Pasadena -- Views (Hotels). Folder 1 of 2., 29 items (Folder 17)
  ALSO SHELVED WITH ROLLED PHOTOS.
- Pasadena -- Views (Hotels). Folder 2 of 2., 40 items (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Pasadena -- Views (Parks)., 2 items (Folder 19)
- Pasadena -- Views (Residences)., 35 items (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Pasadena -- Views (Schools)., 6 items (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Pasadena -- Views (Streets - Colorado St.)., 7 items (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Pasadena -- Views (Streets)., 8 items (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Pasadena -- Views (Tournament of Roses)., 15 items (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Pasadena -- Views (Treaty Oak)., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Pasadena -- Views., 25 items (Folder 10)
- Pasha, Stone., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Paso Robles, Calif., 22 items (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Pater, Walter Horatio, 1839-1894, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Patey, Jane, 1842-1894, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Patterson, Robert, 1891-1952, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Patti, Adelina, 1843-1919, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 11)
- Pauley, Edwin W., 1903-1981, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Paulina, Mlle. -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Peabody, George, 1795-1869., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Peking -- Views., 9 items (Folder 15)
- Pendleton, Ore. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 16)
- Penitentials., 1 item (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Pennsylvania -- Views., 20 items (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Pepper, Claude Denson, 1900-1989., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Perez, Eulalia, 1737-1876, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Perin, Glover, 1823-1890., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965., 1 item (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Perkins, Milo Randolph, 1900-, 1 item (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Pernault Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 24)
- Perris Irrigating Tunnel, 1 item (Folder 26)
- Perris, Calif. -- Views., 7 items (Folder 25)
- Perry, J.W.S. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Peters, Thomas Kimwood, 1884-1974, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Peterson, W.H., 2 items (Folder 29)
- Petrified Forest National Monument., 19 items (Folder 30)
- Pfeiffer State Redwood Park, Calif., 1 item (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Philippi, Jacob -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 56, Folder 32)
- Philippine Islands -- Views. Folder 1 of 2., 85 items (Box 56, Folder 33)
- Philippine Islands -- Views. Folder 2 of 2., 17 items (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Phillips, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Phillips, George S., 2 items (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Phillips, Joseph Duke -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Phillips, Wendell, 1811-1884., 3 items (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Phillpotts, Adelaide Eden., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Phoenix, Arizona, 3 items (Folder 7)
- Phonograph -- Views., 3 items (Folder 8)
- Photographers -- Portraits., 9 items (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 1 of 7). (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 1 of 7)., 18 items (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 2 of 7)., 43 items (Folder 2)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 3 of 7)., 16 items (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 4 of 7)., 16 items (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 5 of 7)., 19 items (Folder 5)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 6 of 7)., 11 items (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Photography - 19th Century - California - Portraits (Folder 7 of 7)., 5 items (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Photography - 19th Century - Los Angeles - Portraits., 52 items (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Photography - 19th Century - San Diego - Portraits., 12 items (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Photography - 19th Century - San Francisco - Portraits., 53 items (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 1 of 16)., 19 items (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 10 of 16)., 63 items (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 11 of 16)., 63 items (Folder 7)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 12 of 16)., 85 items (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 13 of 16)., 65 items (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 14 of 16)., 87 items (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 15 of 16)., 29 items (Folder 3)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 16 of 16)., 42 items (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 2 of 16)., 22 items (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 3 of 16)., 40 items (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 4 of 16)., 41 items (Folder 7)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 5 of 16)., 40 items (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 6 of 16)., 63 items (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 7 of 16)., 60 items (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 8 of 16)., 63 items (Folder 4)
- Photography - 19th Century - U.S. - Portraits (Folder 9 of 16)., 71 items (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Photography - 19th Century - Victorian - Continental Carte-de-visites., 135 items (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Photography - 19th Century - Victorian - English., 80 items (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Photography - 19th Century - Victorian - Views (Art). (folder 1 of 3), 103 items (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Photography - 19th Century - Victorian - Views (Art). (folder 2 of 3), 90 items (Folder 1)
- Photography - 19th Century - Victorian - Views (Art). (folder 3 of 3), 96 items (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Photography - 19th Century - Views., 36 items (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Photography - 20th Century., 30 items (Folder 12)
- Photography - Apparatus and Supplies -- Views., 24 items (Folder 10)
- Photography - History -- Views., 16 items (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Phototelegraphy -- Views., 29 items (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Pickford, Mary, 1893-1979, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 14)
- Pico Family -- Portrait., 32 items (Folder 15)
- Pierce, Charles Chester, Family -- Portrait., 6 items (Folder 16)
- Pierce, Franklin, pres. U.S., 1804-1869, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Piercy, Calif. -- Views., 50 items (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Pike, George H. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Pike's Peak, Colo. -- Views., 35 items (Folder 2)
- Pine Valley, Calif. -- Views., 10 items (Folder 3)
- Pinnacles National Monument., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Pinza, Ezio., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Pioneers -- Calif. -- Portraits., 6 items (Folder 6)
- Pismo Beach, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 7)
- Placerita Canyon., 12 items (Folder 8)
- Plank Roads -- Arizona -- Views., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Plano, Tulare Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Playa del Ray, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Pleasants, J.E., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Plumas Imperial Mine, Plumas Co., Calif., 7 items (Folder 13)
- Plummer Family -- Portrait., 33 items (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Pocatello, Ida. -- Views., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Point Loma, San Diego Co., Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 16)
- Police -- Views., 18 items (Folder 17)
- Pollock, Channing, 1880-1946., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Pomona., 52 items (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Ponselle, Rosa, 1897-1981., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Poole, Paul Falconer., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Port Hueneme, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Folder 23)
- Porta Costa, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Porter, Bernard Harden, 1911-2004., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Porter, Cole, 1893-1964, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Porter, David Dixon, 1813-1891., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Porter, David, 1780-1843., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Porterville, Calif., 3 items (Folder 28)
- Portland, Ore. -- Views., 12 items (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Poston, Charles D., 1 item (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Potsdam, Ger., 4 items (Folder 31)
- Pottery -- Views. Folder 1 of 2., 79 items (Folder 32)
- Pottery -- Views. Folder 2 of 2., 42 items (Folder 1)
- Powell, Lawrence Clark, 1906-2001, -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Powell, Lyman Pierson, 1866-1946., 3 items (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Power Plants -- Views., 7 items (Folder 4)
- Powers, Benjamin N., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Powys, John Cowper, 1872-1963, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Pratt, Ernest Mitchell. (Photographs from Collection 2109)., 23 items (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Precious Stones -- Views., 15 items (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Prescott, Ariz. -- Views., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Presley, Elvis, 1935-1977., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Printing Machinery and Supplies -- Views., 27 items (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Procter, Bryan Waller, 1787-1874, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Prokosch, Frederic, 1906-1989., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Promontory Point, Utah -- Views., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Provo, Utah -- Views., 15 items (Folder 15)
- Prudhomme Family -- Portrait., 12 items (Folder 16)
- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Pueblo, Colo. -- Views., 13 items (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Puente, Calif., 14 items (Folder 19)
- Pulp Magaizines -- Views., 37 items (Folder 20)
- Putnam, Herbert, 1861-1955., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Putnam, Mrs. Nina (Wilcox), 1888-1962., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Quiller-Couch, Sir Arthur Thomas, 1863-1944., 1 item (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Quincy, Calif., 5 items (Folder 24)
- Quincy, Josiah, 1772-1864, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 25)
- Radio Announcing -- Views., 6 items (Folder 27)
- Radio Antennas -- Views., 7 items (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Radio Apparatus and Supplies -- Views., 28 items (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Radio Broadcasting -- Views., 31 items (Folder 29)
- Radio Direction Finders -- Views., 2 items (Folder 1)
- Radio Facsimile -- Views., 4 items (Folder 2)
- Radio Receivers and Reception -- Views., 9 items (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Radio Stations -- Views., 2 items (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Radio Transmitters and Transmissions -- Views., 14 items (Folder 5)
- Radium Hot Springs, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 6)
- Railroads -- Views (Accidents)., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Railroads -- Views (Bridges)., 16 items (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Railroads -- Views (Canadian National Railways)., 18 items (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Railroads -- Views (Cars). Folder 1 of 2., 32 items (Folder 10)
- Railroads -- Views (Cars). Folder 2 of 2., 41 items (Folder 11)
- Railroads -- Views (Central Pacific Company)., 11 items (Folder 12)
- Railroads -- Views (Constructions)., 11 items (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Railroads -- Views (Freight)., 11 items (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Railroads -- Views (Great Northen Railway)., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Railroads -- Views (Locomotives). Folder 1 of 5., 64 items (Folder 16)
- Railroads -- Views (Locomotives). Folder 2 of 5., 42 items (Folder 17)
- Railroads -- Views (Locomotives). Folder 3 of 5., 61 items (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Railroads -- Views (Locomotives). Folder 4 of 5., 43 items (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Railroads -- Views (Locomotives). Folder 5 of 5., 28 items (Folder 3)
- Railroads -- Views (San Diego and Arizona Railway)., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Railroads -- Views (Southern Pacific Company)., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Railroads -- Views (Stations). (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Railroads -- Views (Stations)., 30 items (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Railroads -- Views (Track)., 28 items (Folder 7)
- Railroads -- Views (U.S. History)., 19 items (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Ramboz, John Henry, 1879-1960, -- Portrait. (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Ramboz, John Henry, 1879-1960, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Ramirez Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Ramona, Cali. -- Views., 1 item (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Ramona's Marriage Place. (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Rancho Agua Caliente, Sonoma Co., Calif., 3 items (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Rancho Agua Hedionda, San Diego Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Rancho Aguaje de la Centinela, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Rancho Azusa, Los Angeles co., Calif., 3 items (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Rancho Bolsa de San Cayetano, Monterey Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Rancho Cahuenga -- Views., 1 item (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Rancho Camulos, Ventura Co., Calif., 14 items (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Rancho Ca?on de Santa Ana, Orange Co., Calif., 10 items (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Rancho de la Asuncion, San Luis Obispo Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Rancho Ex-Misi?n de San Fernando, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Rancho Guajome, San Diego Co., Calif., 19 items (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Rancho Huasna, San Luis Obispo Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Rancho Jurupa, Riverside Co., Calif., 3 items (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Rancho La Ballona, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 7 items (Folder 8)
- Rancho La Cienega o Poso de la Tijera, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Rancho La Puente, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Rancho Las Virgenes, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Rancho Los Cerritos, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 5 items (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Rancho Los Ojitos, Monterey Co., Calif., 2 items (Folder 13)
- Rancho Ojai, Ventura Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Rancho Omochumnes, Sacramento Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Rancho Paso de Bartolo Viejo (or) San Rafael, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 7 items (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Rancho Petaluma, Sonoma Co., Calif., 4 items (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Rancho Rincon de San Pascual, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Rancho Rincon, San Bernadino Co., Calif., 6 items (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Rancho San Antonio, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Rancho San Bernardino, San Luis Obispo Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Rancho San Carlos de Jonata, Santa Barbara Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Rancho San Jose, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 14 items (Folder 23)
- Rancho San Miguel, Ventura Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Rancho San Pablo, Contra Costa Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Rancho San Pedro, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Rancho San Pedro, San Mateo Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Rancho San Rafael, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 3 items (Folder 29)
- Rancho Santa Ana del Chino, San Bernardino Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Rancho Santa Ana, Ventura Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Rancho Santa Anita, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 3 items (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Rancho Sante Fe, Calif. -- Views., 20 items (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Randall, Albert Borland, 1879-1945, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Randsburg., 18 items (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Ranke, Leopold von, 1795-1806., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Raskob, John J., 1879-1950., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Raton, N.M. -- Views., 32 items (Folder 38)
- Raymond, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 39)
- Reboun -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Rebout Family -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Rector, William., 1 item (Folder 42)
- Red Bluff, Calif. -- Views., 18 items (Folder 43)
- Red Cross -- Views., 10 items (Folder 44)
- Redgrave, Vanesss, 1937- -- Portrait. (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Redlands, Calif. -- Views., 17 items (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Redlands, University of, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Redondo Beach, Calif. -- Views., 16 items (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Redondo Hotel, Redondo Beach, Calif. -- Views., 9 items (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Redwood City, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Redwood Highway, Calif., 57 items (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Redwood Highway, California -- Views. (Folder 7)
- Reid, Mayne, 1818-1883, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Reinach, Salomon, 1858-1932., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Reine -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Reiner, Fritz, 1888-1963., 1 item (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Remenyi, Edward -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Renaissance Pleasure Faire, Southern California -- Views., 30 items (Folder 12)
- Reno, Nev. -- Views., 2 items (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Requena Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 14)
- Reseda., 39 items (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Rethberg, Elisabeth, 1894-1976., 1 item (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Reuter, Fritz, 1810-1874., 1 item (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Revolutionists, Mexican -- Views., 6 items (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Rexroth, Kenneth, 1905-1982, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Reyes Family -- Portrait., 16 items (Folder 20)
- Rhodesia, Southern -- Views., 18 items (Folder 21)
- Richards, Richard, 1916- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Richfield, Utah -- Views., 1 item (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Richmond, Va. -- Views., 2 items (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Ridgway, Colo. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 25)
- Riis, Jacob August, 1849-1914., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Rikhoff, Jean -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)